CLIVE MACHADO

Software Engineer

clivemchd@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/clive-machado 04901625739885 Munich. Bayaria

I am Javascript developer who specializes in frontend development. There are always more things to do in the world and I love to solve problems. With a great experience on modern technology I can bring your ideas to life and also find you the solution.

Core Skills

Web Performance, Problem Solving,
Code Review,
Web Application Development,
Maintainability, Clean Coding,
Skill Development, Front-End Development,
JavaScript, HTML5, css, Sass, React.js,
AngularJS, Redux.js, TypeScript, REST Api,
TanStack Query, React hook form,
Material UI, Mobx, NodeJS, Vite

Education

University of Mumbai

Jan 2014 - Jan 2017

Master of Computer Applications (MCA) GPA 7.05

Languages

Marathi ((Native)) English (B2) Hindi (B2)

Work Experience

Software Engineer

Mar 2022 - Present

<u>Sport Alliance GmbH</u> | Munich, Bavaria, Germany

My responsibilities as a developer was maintaining one of our products called Magicline, MySports which are a Gym management software which uses ReactJS, Typescript, Mobx among others. Later helped build a developer integrations dashboard entirely for other developers to configure the properties for the api's they consume.

 ReactJS, Material UI, Typescript, Mobx, Reat Hook Form, TanStack Query, Vite

Sr. Frontend Engineer

Jan 2017 - Feb 2022

Raw Engineering | Vasai Virar, Maharashtra, India

Worked for a product Built.io which was a Backend as a Service (BaaS). My responsibilities was entirely maintaining the frontend for it. Later transitioned into a senior role and took upon the responsibility for its new clients The NBA. I lead and architected an entire admin dashboard for the NBA using ReactJS, Redux and Typescript. Also worked on a SDK called OPiN which is embedded in the NBA and the F1 websites, built using Typescript.

ReactJS, Typescript, AngularJS, NodeJS, Redux, HTML & CSS